rhbgroup.com 2016-11-27

# Welcome to RHB Banking Group

RHB Banking Group (" **RHB"** ) values your trust in us and respects the need to maintain the security and confidentiality of information that you provide to us, whether or not you are a RHB customer (" **Customer** "), a customer who has registered for our internet banking services (" **Registered User** ") [hereinafter collectively referred as **“RHB Customer”** ] or a visitor to our website (" **Visitor** "). RHB is committed to protect each individual's privacy. That is our pledge to you.

This Privacy Policy sets out RHB's general practices relating to the use and storage of the information you have provided to us online via this website. If you wish to obtain more information on the manner in which RHB processes your information, please refer to the **[PDPA Privacy Notice](http://rhbgroup.com/general-info/personal-data-protection-act)**

  1. **Information Received  
**We receive various types of information via this website when you make a general inquiry or provide feedback, when you make an appointment to see our Customer Service Personnel or where you are applying for new products or services, including but not limited to the following:   

    1. information that personally identifies you, such as your name, NRIC/passport number, contact details or background information (" **Personal Information** ");
    2. if you are a RHB Customer, your account number, financial information or other information relevant to your account with RHB; and
    3. information consisting your physical/mental health ( **“Sensitive Information”** ), if any.
  2. **Purpose of Collection**

We will process the information you have provided to us for any of the following purposes, depending on the circumstances in which you provided the said information to us:-

    1. Applications for internet banking services via RHB’s websiteYour customer information which is already in our possession, along with any additional information you may provide via this website will be used to provide you with the additional internet banking services you have requested. 
    2. Visitor to our website

If you are a Visitor to our website, you are not required to provide us with any information about you, unless you are making a general inquiry, providing feedback, requesting for an appointment with our Customer Service personnel or where you are applying for new products or services

  3. **Cookies**  
A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier which we transfer to your hard drive through your web browser when you visit our website. Whether you are a RHB Customer or Visitor, as you browse through our website, you may be subject to the use of cookies to retain information about your web browser and usage preferences for general visitor analysis. This will help us to improve your user experience on our site. Cookies may also be used to compile aggregate information about areas of our website that are visited most frequently. By accessing our website, you agree to us placing cookies on your computer or device. If you wish to reject our cookie, you can configure your browser to do so. 
  4. **Confidentiality** **and Security of Information**

We shall strive to ensure that security measures are exemplary and that all confidential information received shall only be used in the course of providing financial services to you.

    1. We assure that only proven development tools and techniques are used, whether they relate to security or encryption technologies. These are subject to risk analyses, and guidelines are regularly tested and updated to ensure that information received from RHB Customer/Visitor through the Internet is secured.
    2. We assure that access to information by RHB employees or its agents are limited through system access control mechanisms and positive authentication systems. We also maintain mechanisms such as audit logs and electronic journals.
    3. All RHB employees are bound by a code of ethics and we assure that the privacy of your information is protected by a confidentiality agreement at all times.
    4. If your information is to be shared with agents, affiliates and/or any other third party as stated in this Privacy Policy, your information is also protected by a confidentiality agreement at all times.

  5. **Use and Sharing of Information**
    1. We assure you that the whole or any part of the information received from you shall not be divulged, reproduced or used for any purpose other than that as stated in this Privacy Policy, or where applicable, our **[PDPA Privacy Notice](http://rhbgroup.com/general-info/personal-data-protection-act)**  unless duly authorised by you or in the restricted circumstances permitted by law.
    2. However, we do reserve the right to use the information provided by you to perform necessary credit checks or to assist other financial institutions in assessing your credit worthiness and collection of debts.
    3. RHB may share specific information about you, if you are a RHB Customer, only with an agent or affiliate (including members of the RHB Banking Group) so as to share our full range of products and services with you.
    4. If you are a Visitor to our website, RHB may also share non-specific information about you whether with an agent or affiliate or other reputable third parties, so as to advise you of opportunities and offers that may be of interest to you.
    5. Third parties with whom RHB shares your information are not permitted to retain any customer information unless you have specifically expressed interest in their products or services and/or have authorised the same.

  6. **Limit on Distribution of Information  
**If you are a RHB Customer, you have the option of limiting or preventing distribution of information by notifying RHB in writing by post or facsimile transmission to the address and facsimile number as stated in our **[PDPA Privacy Notice](http://rhbgroup.com/general-info/personal-data-protection-act).**

  7. **Accessibility and Accuracy of Information**  
We strive to ensure that RHB Customer’s information is accurate and kept up to date. However, in order to ensure that your records are kept up to date, we encourage you to assist us by informing us in the event that your records require to be updated, are found to be incomplete or inaccurate in the manner indicated in our **[PDPA Privacy Notice](http://rhbgroup.com/general-info/personal-data-protection-act)**. You may also access your information in a similar manner. 

If you are a Visitor, you also have the right to access and/or correct any of your information currently in our possession by contacting :   
Banking Services : +603 9206 8118  
Investment Services : +603 2071 9000  
Insurance Services : +603 2180 3000

  8. **Customer Questions or Complaints  
**RHB honours its commitment to protect its customers' privacy. If you have any queries, concerns or complaints on customer information or services, please contact us via post or facsimile transmission to us at the following address, or call us.

RHB Bank   
Service Quality & Service Recovery Management  
RHB Banking Group  
Level 6, Menara AA  
Jalan Tun Razak  
50400 Kuala Lumpur 

Telephone : 03-92068090  
Facsimile : 03-92068088  
Email : [customer.service@rhbgroup.com](mailto:customer.service@rhbgroup.com)

© 2015 RHB Banking Group. Subject to Terms & Conditions of Use.

  1. RHB 
  2. Malaysia 
  3. General Info 
  4. Privacy Policy 

You are about to enter a third party website and RHB Banking Group's privacy policy will cease to apply.

This link is provided for your convenience only, and shall not be considered or construed as an endorsement or verification of such linked website or its contents by RHB Banking Group.

RHB Banking Group also makes no warranties as to the status of this link or information contained in the website you are about to access.
